So, how does the AI image generator of pixel or work?
That's basically very, very similar to all the other chatbots
and all the other generators that we had, you know.
So, over here we have a prompt.
And as you see, it can either be fast or pro or ultra, right?
And each takes different kind of credits, you know.
Now, if this is zero credits remaining, I don't know why, because I didn't do anything with its AI.
So, I'm wondering if the free account doesn't have any credits at all, that would be weird.
But whatever. So, when it says free AI tool, this is probably lying.
Is it? Isn't it?
Whatever. So, as you see over here, we don't have anything new.
We have a prompt and then we click on generate.
But the point here is that we don't have any kind of credits to do that.
So, it will have an error.
We'll see an error.
For example, I say, I want to have a photo of an owl, let's say, cooking dinner, right?
So, this is my prompt.
And if I click generate, you'll see that, yep, it says that we need to buy some kind of a
plan or pricing in order to do that.
But whatever, it also has an image generator.
We don't even want to use it because it's nothing special.
You know, there's plenty of them in today's world, especially.